

## **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Email komalshimpi91198@gmail.com

Mobile (+91) 9834217504

Total work experience 3 Years 1 Month

#### **KEY SKILLS**

ASP.NET

**Azure Fundamental** 

ASP.Net MVC

**NUnit** 

ADO.Net

Visual Studio Code

Asp.Net Core

MVC

**Entity Framework** 

Azure

Angular

Web API

C#

ASP

.NET Core

.NET

**Data Structures** 

SQL Server

Jenkins

# Komal Dhanraj Shimpi

**Associate Consultant** 

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I'm having around 3+ year of experience as a Full Stack .Net Developer. Expertise in .Net, Asp.net MVC, .net Core, C#, Entity Framework, Web API, Angular JS,TyepeScript, HTML, Css, JavaScript, SQL Server, Azure, Unit Testing, Postman, Data structure. Tools-JIRA, Git and Bitbucket/TFS.

#### **EDUCATION**

2021 ¶ MS/M.Sc(Science)

North Maharashtra University (NMU)

2019 9 B.Sc

North Maharashtra University (NMU)

2016 | XIIth

**English** 

Y Xth

Marathi

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sep 2024 -Present

2014

**Associate Consultant** 

## Infosys

Working with Developmen team. Worked on Front End as well as Backend Technologies. In Frontend worked on the building UI, Services angular component, also wrote unit test cases using Jasmin and Karma Framework. In Bankend developed services for UI components using Node JS.

Technologies: Angular, Typescript, JavaScript, CSS, Node JS, AWS.

Jan 2023 - Sep 2024

Software Engineer

## Rainbow infotech pvt ltd

I was working with development team to develop and enhance existing web application. Participated in developing new featute, new and existing bug fixes independently, production support. Web Services

OOPS

Bitbucket

JIRA

GIT

**JSON** 

HTML

CSS

## **OTHER PERSONAL DETAILS**

City

Pune

Country

INDIA

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

Technologies: Angular, TypeScrpt, JavaScript, CSS, .Net core API, C#, Sql Serve.

Dec 2021 - Jan 2023 Software Engineer

## **Cognopi Solutions**

Worked on developing web application using ASP.Net MVC, .Net Core Web API, SQL Server.

## **Projects**

120 Days

## **Academic Collaborative Network**

Academic collaborative network has been developed to integrate teacher's of multiple colleges under one platform where Content/Resources will be shared on different streams. When required teachers from registered colleges can visit the site and share or download the necessary content

#### **COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS**

Net Full Stack - 6 Months Diploma Certification